Noah J. Holt

Email: noahjmholt@gmail.com

Cell: 803.468.3236

Last Updated: May 2024

Willing to Relocate: Negotiable

Security Clearance: Able to Obtain (no criminal history) Willing to Travel: Yes

EXPERIENCE SUMMARY

Pursuing a full-time career in Computer Science beginning late May 2024. Wanting to explore the field of computer science and reach my niche. Interests I have found in the field include app development, security, networks, and data science. Though I have explored these fields, I feel I have barely scratched their surfaces leaving curiosity and interests to explore.

Goal and results oriented communicator, training, and ability to work well in highly stressful situations and environments. One year of education based IT troubleshooting and assistance, with an extra 2+ years of customer service and relationship building experience.

EDUCATION

University of Colorado-Colorado Springs: Bachelor's in Computer Science, May 2024 PIMA Medical Institute: Associates of Veterinary Technology, Aug 2018 - May 2020

CERTIFICATIONS

CompTIA A+, Cert #: COMP001022097585

Next: CompTIA Net+ (Jun 2024), and Security+ (Oct 2024)

SUMMARY OF SKILLS, TOOLS, AND TECHNOLOGIES:

Java, C, C#, C++, R, PythonObject Oriented Programming KnowledgeMicrosoft Office SuitesDocker and AWSBash ScriptingTrainer & EducationGit and GitHubWindows and Linux Operating SystemRugby CoachWordPress, Django, TypeScriptIT Service Desk (Tier 1 and Tier 2)CPR & BLS

Restful API Agile frameworks

PROJECT WORK EXPERIENCE

Discord Worm, Class Project: Jan 2024 - May 2024

In a group of four, created virus to traverse Discord servers and users to collect data.

- In group of four, built computer worm to explore Discord vulnerabilities.
 - Using C#, modified discord API's to have bots collect data on users in the servers they are a part of.
 - Used restful API and typescript to connect Database and worm bots to pass information in and retrieve with Discord bot commands.
 - O Disclaimer: These bots were not released to non-test servers and their travel functionality was never activated.

Secret Santa Wish List, Class Project: Sep 2023 – Dec 2023

Created wish list Web app for users to login, add items viewable the public.

- Implemented CRUD application with one-to-many relationship for database.
- Using an agile workflow, Django for web development, docker for storage and AWS for hosting

EXPERIENCE DETAILS

UCCS IT, Colorado Springs, CO, IT Technician: Mar 2022 – Nov 2023

- Provided Tier 1 technical support as dedicated Help Desk professional providing technical support in a 15,000+ student and 1,000+ faculty user environment.
- Problem-solver that can communicate with users at all levels of technical proficiency.
- Troubleshoot, resolve, and document user help requests for desktop, laptop, mobile, network and peripheral problems. Platforms include Windows, Mac OS X, iOS, Chrome OS, Android.
- Imaging, configuring, and managing of MacOS and Windows machines.
- Troubleshooting: networking, secure VPN, operating systems (iOS, Windows), and printers.
- Maintaining and monitoring 1,000+ machines across campus area network.
- Responsible for teaching/assisting new employees in their daily routines, evaluated performances, critiqued knowledge and performance, and conducted individual assistance.
- Remote administration responsibilities for software and hardware installation across the Campus Area Network, in direct support of students/faulty/staff, and devices.
- Field and implemented intranet and enterprise security policies for the UCCS network infrastructure.

Scheels All Sport, Colorado Springs – Service Shop Technician: Jan 2021 – Feb 2022

• Provided assistance and instructions to customers and fellow associates in maintenance of various products, while providing world class customer service.

Colorado Canine Orthopedics and Rehab – Vet Tech, Technician: Jun 2019 – Mar 2020

• Responsible for performing routine checkups and other medical procedures on animals to ensure their health and well-being. These requirements included communicating with pet parents to determine whether their pet experienced changes in activity or diet, checking an animal's weight, heartbeat, and other vital signs to record in patient files, and assisting other veterinary personnel in taking blood samples or administering medications.

Links:

https://github.com/NoahjmHolt

https://www.linkedin.com/in/noah-holt-23560522b/